{
  "Topic 1: Global Warming": [
    {
      "question_id": "Q1",
      "question": "What is the approximate reference period for the temperature increase?",
      "answer_id": "A1",
      "answer": "Pre-industrial, 1850-1900"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q2",
      "question": "Approximately how many degrees has the global temperature risen since industrialization?",
      "answer_id": "A2",
      "answer": "Approx. 1.5 degrees"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q3",
      "question": "Is there a region where the temperature has risen significantly more?",
      "answer_id": "A3",
      "answer": "The poles, especially the North Pole by up to 6°C"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q4",
      "question": "Besides temperature, what other changes indicate global warming?",
      "answer_id": "A4",
      "answer": "Less pack ice, melting glaciers, less snow cover, rising sea level, growing ocean acidification"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q5",
      "question": "What causes more direct damage, the absolute temperature increase or the rate of change?",
      "answer_id": "A5",
      "answer": "The absolute change has been higher in earth´s history but over a much longer period, the"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q6",
      "question": "How high are the yearly global cost of climate related natural disasters? >1, >10, >100 bn",
      "answer_id": "A6",
      "answer": ">100 bn USD"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q7",
      "question": "What can cause natural climate change?",
      "answer_id": "A7",
      "answer": "Changes in Earth´s position to the sun (eccentricity, precession, tilt), volcanoes (dual effect"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q8",
      "question": "What are the timescales for natural climate change?",
      "answer_id": "A8",
      "answer": "Tens of thousands and hundreds of thousands of years (see orbital changes)"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q9",
      "question": "Which effect is the only one that can explain climate change in simulations?",
      "answer_id": "A9",
      "answer": "CO2 emissions"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q10",
      "question": "How old is the knowledge about the influence of CO2 on the climate – 170, 70, 20, 10 years?",
      "answer_id": "A10",
      "answer": "Approximately 170 years"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q11",
      "question": "What has a higher heat absorption capacity, the atmosphere or the oceans and how long",
      "answer_id": "A11",
      "answer": "The oceans have a much higher heat capacity than the atmosphere: While the atmosphere"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q12",
      "question": "What is the average solar irradiance per m² – 3.4, 34, 340, 3400, or 34000 W/m²?",
      "answer_id": "A12",
      "answer": "340 W/m²"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q13",
      "question": "What is the albedo factor?",
      "answer_id": "A13",
      "answer": "The portion of solar radiation reflected by a surface; 0 for absorption, 1 for total reflection, , 0,8"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q14",
      "question": "What distinguishes the Earth and the Moon during day and night?",
      "answer_id": "A14",
      "answer": "Temperature difference moderate on Earth due to its atmosphere, big on the Moon due to a"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q15",
      "question": "In which spectrum (name) lie the peaks of the sun´s and the earth´s irradiance?",
      "answer_id": "A15",
      "answer": "The peak of solar irradiance is in the visible spectrum the peak of Earth´s irradiance is in the"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q16",
      "question": "How do greenhouse gases work?",
      "answer_id": "A16",
      "answer": "Absorption, movement of molecules (heat), reemission of infrared light also back to Earth."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q17",
      "question": "Name two significant greenhouse gases besides CO2?",
      "answer_id": "A17",
      "answer": "Methane and nitrous oxide."
    }
  ],
  "Topic 2: Carbon": [
    {
      "question_id": "Q18",
      "question": "What makes the element carbon so special?",
      "answer_id": "A18",
      "answer": "The ability to form so many different bonds with itself and other atoms."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q19",
      "question": "Name bond combinations for Carbon:",
      "answer_id": "A19",
      "answer": "4x1, 2x2, 2+1+1, 3+1"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q20",
      "question": "How do you estimate enthalpies of combustion?",
      "answer_id": "A20",
      "answer": "As the difference in bond energies between reactants and products."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q21",
      "question": "What is the difference between lower and higher heating values?",
      "answer_id": "A21",
      "answer": "The higher heating value includes the enthalpy of condensation of water formed in the"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q22",
      "question": "What is produced during photosynthesis from 6 CO2 and 6 H2O?",
      "answer_id": "A22",
      "answer": "C6H12O6 Glucose + 6 O2"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q23",
      "question": "What is the maximum theoretical efficiency of photosynthesis?",
      "answer_id": "A23",
      "answer": "About 4.6%"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q24",
      "question": "What is the practical efficiency of photosynthesis?",
      "answer_id": "A24",
      "answer": "Mostly under 2%, often as low as 0.4%"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q25",
      "question": "What happens during the breakdown of cellulose to oil and gas?",
      "answer_id": "A25",
      "answer": "Removal of oxygen from molecules."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q26",
      "question": "When did coal primarily form?",
      "answer_id": "A26",
      "answer": "About 300 million years ago in the carboniferous period."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q27",
      "question": "When did oil primarily form?",
      "answer_id": "A27",
      "answer": "About 170 million years ago in the Mesozoic, in particular in the Jurassic period."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q28",
      "question": "Where is a very high natural concentration of C?",
      "answer_id": "A28",
      "answer": "In living organisms, where carbon forms 50% of the dry matter"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q29",
      "question": "Where is the most carbon bound in Earth's habitat: in the forest, at the ocean surface, or in",
      "answer_id": "A29",
      "answer": "In the deep sea"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q30",
      "question": "Why is glucose a poor fuel?",
      "answer_id": "A30",
      "answer": "There is too little hydrogen and too much oxygen in the molecule – meaning it is somewhere"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q31",
      "question": "Why do wood (polysaccharide cellulose), ethanol, or glucose produce more CO2 when",
      "answer_id": "A31",
      "answer": "Again, as before, there is too little hydrogen and too much oxygen in the molecule – meaning"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q32",
      "question": "What effect do the oceans have on the rate of global warming?",
      "answer_id": "A32",
      "answer": "The oceans not only absorb a lot of CO2, but their sheer mass also slows down the"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q33",
      "question": "Is the air-water equilibrium for CO2 temperature-dependent, and if so, how?",
      "answer_id": "A33",
      "answer": "At higher temperatures, water dissolves less CO2."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q34",
      "question": "Is the equilibrium of CO2 in the oceans static or dynamic?",
      "answer_id": "A34",
      "answer": "Dynamic, CO2 is absorbed from the atmosphere into the cold water currents at the poles"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q35",
      "question": "What is a positive feedback loop in global warming?",
      "answer_id": "A35",
      "answer": "A positive feedback loop builds on a self-inforcing mechanism, like warming melts pack ice,"
    }
  ],
  "Topic 3: Reporting": [
    {
      "question_id": "Q36",
      "question": "At which three levels are greenhouse gas emissions reported?",
      "answer_id": "A36",
      "answer": "Greenhouse gas inventories are calculated for countries/nations, for companies and for"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q37",
      "question": "Which institutions developed the leading standards for GHG reporting?",
      "answer_id": "A37",
      "answer": "UN (UNFCCC) for nations, GHG Protocol (World Resources Institute, World Business Council"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q38",
      "question": "What was the climate saving scope of the Rio Earth Summit, the Kyotoy Protocol and the",
      "answer_id": "A38",
      "answer": "Rio: Stabilize GHG conc. to prevent dangerous interfe-rence with climate system;"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q39",
      "question": "What is the share of energy use in emissions globally and in Germany?",
      "answer_id": "A39",
      "answer": ">70% and >80%"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q40",
      "question": "How are emissions collected, i.e., directly or indirectly?",
      "answer_id": "A40",
      "answer": "Through multiplication of activity data (km/y) multiplied with emission factors (g CO2/km)"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q41",
      "question": "Give a basic example of consumption and emission factor.",
      "answer_id": "A41",
      "answer": "Example: Electricity consumption in kWh and CO2 value per kWh in the electricity grid"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q42",
      "question": "Name two of the top 5 GHG emitters as countries:",
      "answer_id": "A42",
      "answer": "China, USA, India, Russia, Japan"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q43",
      "question": "Name two of the top 5 GHG per capita emitters as countries:",
      "answer_id": "A43",
      "answer": "Australia, Canada, Saudi Arabia, USA, Russia"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q44",
      "question": "By when do most countries want to be climate neutral?",
      "answer_id": "A44",
      "answer": "2050"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q45",
      "question": "What does the Greenhouse Gas Protocol define?",
      "answer_id": "A45",
      "answer": "Emissions reports for companies and products"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q46",
      "question": "Define Scope 1 emissions, define Scope 2 emissions, define Scope 3 emissions",
      "answer_id": "A46",
      "answer": "Scope 1 (direct emissions from owned or controlled sources)"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q47",
      "question": "Give examples of companies with high and low Scope 1 emissions:",
      "answer_id": "A47",
      "answer": "steel, cement, and chemicals with high emissions;"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q48",
      "question": "Give examples of companies with high Scope 3 upstream emissions:",
      "answer_id": "A48",
      "answer": "Plastic part manufacturers (as a lot of emissions occur upstream in the chemical industry)"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q49",
      "question": "Give examples of companies with high Scope 3 downstream emissions:",
      "answer_id": "A49",
      "answer": "Refineries (as most products are being burnt downstream by customers as fuels)"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q50",
      "question": "What does the Science Based Targets initiative require of its signatories?",
      "answer_id": "A50",
      "answer": "To adhere to the 1.5°C target and fulfill and report yearly emission reductions in the order of"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q51",
      "question": "Calculate the annual emissions of company X: electricity consumption 1,000,000 kWh,",
      "answer_id": "A51",
      "answer": "350 t + 540 t + 576 t = 1466 t."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q52",
      "question": "Explain the Product Carbon Footprint (PCF)",
      "answer_id": "A52",
      "answer": "A Product Carbon Footprint (PCF) refers to the total greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q53",
      "question": "What is meant by a cradle to gate PCF:",
      "answer_id": "A53",
      "answer": "Emissions from raw material extraction to sale."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q54",
      "question": "What does cradle to grave mean:",
      "answer_id": "A54",
      "answer": "From raw material extraction to disposal/incineration?"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q55",
      "question": "How are Product Carbon Footprints and company emissions related?",
      "answer_id": "A55",
      "answer": "The sum of the product footprints (product quantity x product footprint) must reflect the"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q56",
      "question": "Are there one or more standards for calculating PCF?",
      "answer_id": "A56",
      "answer": "Several national standards."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q57",
      "question": "For which industry was the Together for Sustainability PCF standard developed?",
      "answer_id": "A57",
      "answer": "Chemical industry."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q58",
      "question": "When is allocation necessary in PCF calculation?",
      "answer_id": "A58",
      "answer": "When two products come from one process."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q59",
      "question": "Give examples of foods with a high PCF:",
      "answer_id": "A59",
      "answer": "Beef, cheese, chocolate, coffee."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q60",
      "question": "Give examples of foods with a low PCF:",
      "answer_id": "A60",
      "answer": "Apples, carrots, bananas, peas."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q61",
      "question": "What is the approximate PCF of a pair of sneakers? (1, 10, or 50 kg CO2/pair)",
      "answer_id": "A61",
      "answer": "7-9"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q62",
      "question": "Name two building materials with a high PCF.",
      "answer_id": "A62",
      "answer": "Aluminum and stainless steel"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q63",
      "question": "What is the approximate PCF of a Golf-class combustion engine vehicle?",
      "answer_id": "A63",
      "answer": "6 t CO2"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q64",
      "question": "What is the approximate PCF of a comparable electric car?",
      "answer_id": "A64",
      "answer": "11 t CO2"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q65",
      "question": "What accounts for the difference?",
      "answer_id": "A65",
      "answer": "The battery production including the production of lithium is energy- and emission-intensive"
    }
  ],
  "Topic 4: Energy": [
    {
      "question_id": "Q66",
      "question": "Name the two main categories of energy:",
      "answer_id": "A66",
      "answer": "potential energy and kinetic energy."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q67",
      "question": "Name subtypes of potential energy:",
      "answer_id": "A67",
      "answer": "chemical, mechanical, nuclear, gravimetric."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q68",
      "question": "Name subtypes of kinetic energy:",
      "answer_id": "A68",
      "answer": "radiation, heat, motion, sound, electricity."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q69",
      "question": "What percentage of global emissions come from energy, and of that, from heat and electricity:",
      "answer_id": "A69",
      "answer": "approximately 75% combined, and approximately 50% from heat and approximately 25% from"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q70",
      "question": "What is the emission ratio between coal and gas?",
      "answer_id": "A70",
      "answer": "Approximately a factor of 2 for direct heat use and approximately a factor of 3 for electricity"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q71",
      "question": "How does the oxygen content in molecules affect calorific value / heating value and CO2",
      "answer_id": "A71",
      "answer": "Calorific value decreases, and CO2 emissions increase."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q72",
      "question": "What is the share of renewable energies globally (not just electricity, but total)? 0%-10%,",
      "answer_id": "A72",
      "answer": "It's 15%."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q73",
      "question": "What is the efficiency of typical power plants?",
      "answer_id": "A73",
      "answer": "Nuclear power 30%, coal 40%, gas-fired combined heat and power plants >80%"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q74",
      "question": "Define energy efficiency:",
      "answer_id": "A74",
      "answer": "Energy used / Energy input"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q75",
      "question": "What are the approximate efficiency levels of a candle, a classic light bulb, and an LED?",
      "answer_id": "A75",
      "answer": "Approx. 1%, approx. 20%, approx. 40%"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q76",
      "question": "What is the overall efficiency of a chain of processes that individually have efficiencies of",
      "answer_id": "A76",
      "answer": "0.8 * 0.5 * 0.25 = 0.1, so 10%, product rule"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q77",
      "question": "Give an example of an energy conversion with efficiency:",
      "answer_id": "A77",
      "answer": "Example: combustion engine typically 20%, max. 42% or solar module 20%, maximum 47% in"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q78",
      "question": "How much more efficient is an electric vehicle in its use of electricity compared to a A:",
      "answer_id": "A78",
      "answer": "72% to 15%, so 5 to 1"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q79",
      "question": "Which demand (oil, electricity, or gas) fluctuates strongly seasonally and why?",
      "answer_id": "A79",
      "answer": "Gas demand as it is a heating fuel in winter"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q80",
      "question": "Where is electricity demand more dependent on the time of day: In material industry (metal or",
      "answer_id": "A80",
      "answer": "Private households"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q81",
      "question": "Is solar radiation uniform or variable throughout the year in Germany?",
      "answer_id": "A81",
      "answer": "Varying greatly, 10 to 15 times more in midsummer than in winter"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q82",
      "question": "How does solar radiation depend on latitude?",
      "answer_id": "A82",
      "answer": "High at the equator, low at the poles"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q83",
      "question": "Is there a difference in temperature between the equator and the North Pole throughout the",
      "answer_id": "A83",
      "answer": "Yes, in the Northern Hemisphere the difference is small in summer and large in winter."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q84",
      "question": "What effect does this difference have?",
      "answer_id": "A84",
      "answer": "It acts as a driving force for wind currents"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q85",
      "question": "When can more wind energy be harvested, in summer or winter?",
      "answer_id": "A85",
      "answer": "Winter."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q86",
      "question": "What is meant by \"dark doldrums\"?",
      "answer_id": "A86",
      "answer": "A period without solar energy (fog, clouds, or darkness) and little wind (calm)."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q87",
      "question": "What is meant by \"demand-side management\" in the context of energy?",
      "answer_id": "A87",
      "answer": "Shifting consumption from times of high demand to times of low demand and storing energy"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q88",
      "question": "Give examples of intensive private electricity consumers where the use can generally be",
      "answer_id": "A88",
      "answer": "Washing machine and dryer, and charging electric cars."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q89",
      "question": "Which fossil fuel is stored in Germany and the EU, partly in national storage facilities?",
      "answer_id": "A89",
      "answer": "Natural gas."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q90",
      "question": "What are relevant energy storage facilities for renewable energies?",
      "answer_id": "A90",
      "answer": "Pumped-storage power plants,"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q91",
      "question": "Name the key parameters for evaluating energy storage systems:",
      "answer_id": "A91",
      "answer": "capacity, discharge time, efficiency for charging and discharging cycles = round trip efficiency,"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q92",
      "question": "What influence does the number of storage cycles have on costs?",
      "answer_id": "A92",
      "answer": "The higher the number of cycles, the lower the depreciation costs per cycle"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q93",
      "question": "How long would German pumped-storage power plants last to cover Germany's electricity",
      "answer_id": "A93",
      "answer": "40 min"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q94",
      "question": "How long would all electric car batteries and solar storage systems last to cover electricity",
      "answer_id": "A94",
      "answer": "70 min"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q95",
      "question": "Germany currently has approximately 0.02% of its annual electricity demand as storage",
      "answer_id": "A95",
      "answer": "Approximately 0.2 to 2%, depending on the study."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q96",
      "question": "When is the electricity price lowest on the power exchange?",
      "answer_id": "A96",
      "answer": "When demand is low and renewable energy sources are in high proportion."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q97",
      "question": "How does the Merit Order Principle work in the definition of electricity prices at the German",
      "answer_id": "A97",
      "answer": "All potential suppliers of electricity offer their supplies at their marginal cost and are then"
    }
  ],
  "Topic 5: Sector Solutions": [
    {
      "question_id": "Q98",
      "question": "Which process should be implemented faster: electrification or expansion of renewable",
      "answer_id": "A98",
      "answer": "The renewable electricity production should be developed faster than the growing"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q99",
      "question": "What is plotted on the x-axis and y-axis of a marginal abatement cost curve for CO2",
      "answer_id": "A99",
      "answer": "The x-axis represents the absolute or proportional CO2 reductions achieved through"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q100",
      "question": "How are the measures ordered within the marginal abatement cost curve?",
      "answer_id": "A100",
      "answer": "From left to right, with increasing CO2 avoidance costs"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q101",
      "question": "Task: Roughly prioritize three measures according to their CO2 avoidance costs:",
      "answer_id": "A101",
      "answer": "Result according to CO2 avoidance costs: C) €25/t CO2 A) €100/t CO2 B) €2,000/t CO2"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q102",
      "question": "Which energy producers currently have the lowest levelized cost of energy (LCOE) in",
      "answer_id": "A102",
      "answer": "Solar power and onshore wind."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q103",
      "question": "What is the approximate share of renewable energies in electricity generation in Germany",
      "answer_id": "A103",
      "answer": "Almost 60%, 59% in 2023"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q104",
      "question": "What were the approximate average emissions from electricity generation in 2023?",
      "answer_id": "A104",
      "answer": "350 g CO2/kWh"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q105",
      "question": "In the building sector, what is the market share of heat pump technology in new",
      "answer_id": "A105",
      "answer": ">50% approaching 60%"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q106",
      "question": "What is district heating currently supplied from?",
      "answer_id": "A106",
      "answer": "Waste heat from combustion power plants (hard coal, lignite, natural gas, waste incineration)"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q107",
      "question": "What are refrigerants?",
      "answer_id": "A107",
      "answer": "Materials which boil at low temperature so that they can take up heat through evaporation"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q108",
      "question": "What are the problems with different refrigerants?",
      "answer_id": "A108",
      "answer": "Flammability, toxicity, global warming potential, ozone depletion"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q109",
      "question": "How does a heat pump work, i.e., how does the cycle work?",
      "answer_id": "A109",
      "answer": "Evaporation, compression, condensation, expansion"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q110",
      "question": "Does the coefficient of performance decrease or fall with the source temperature?",
      "answer_id": "A110",
      "answer": "Increases"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q111",
      "question": "Does the coefficient of performance decrease or fall with the sink or application",
      "answer_id": "A111",
      "answer": "Decreases"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q112",
      "question": "Where in Europe are heat pumps most widespread?",
      "answer_id": "A112",
      "answer": "Scandinavia"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q113",
      "question": "Which type of heat pump is widespread in Scandinavia?",
      "answer_id": "A113",
      "answer": "Air/Air Heat Pump"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q114",
      "question": "Give examples of low temperature, medium temperature and high temperature processes in",
      "answer_id": "A114",
      "answer": "Low temperature: cooking and baking in food industry, Medium temperature: e.g."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q115",
      "question": "What is the approximate ratio of emissions during operation between a combustion engine",
      "answer_id": "A115",
      "answer": "Roughly a factor of 3 Combustion engine: approx. 6 kg fuel/100 km * 3 kg CO2/kg fuel = 18"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q116",
      "question": "What is a vapor compressor?",
      "answer_id": "A116",
      "answer": "A process-integrated heat pump, usually in a distillation process."
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q117",
      "question": "Name different hydrogen production processes?",
      "answer_id": "A117",
      "answer": "Steam reforming with natural gas and water, methane pyrolysis, water electrolysis"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q118",
      "question": "What is methane pyrolysis?",
      "answer_id": "A118",
      "answer": "Conversion of CH4 to carbon and hydrogen using heat"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q119",
      "question": "Where is nitrous oxide produced in chemistry?",
      "answer_id": "A119",
      "answer": "For example, in the production of nitric acid for fertilizers or of adipic acid as a monomer for"
    },
    {
      "question_id": "Q120",
      "question": "What type of chemical reactions in material production lead to carbon dioxide?",
      "answer_id": "A120",
      "answer": "The reduction of limestone oxides for cement, of iron oxides for steel and of aluminum oxides"
    }
  ]
}